hound.com 2012-05-13

# Privacy Policy, Online Job Search Engine, Job Search Website | Hound.com

Privacy Policy

**Effective on: (03/01/2010)**

Hound.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and we are firmly devoted to maintaining your trust in us. We work extremely hard at safeguarding our customers' important information and keeping it secure. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand our genuine dedication to preserving your privacy. This Privacy Statement applies to the Site 

[_www.hound.com_](http://www.hound.com/). Confidentiality and discretion are the cornerstones of every job search. We consistently challenge ourselves to rise above every competitor in our honesty and discretion, and we believe we have met this challenge day after day. We have established this Privacy Statement to inform our visitors and users how we collect, use and store the personal information you submit while using our Site. "Personal Information" applies to information that can be used to identify you, such as your name and email address. 

Hound is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, and we are firmly devoted to maintaining your trust in us. We work extremely hard at safeguarding our users' important information and keeping it secure. Our privacy policy is designed to help you understand our genuine dedication to preserving your privacy. 

During the course of your 

[_registration_](http://www.hound.com/) with Hound, we collect certain information in order to set up your account. Hound will never sell any personal information about any of our users to any third parties. We will never sell your email address or any other contact information to any third parties for any purpose. We collect personal information such as your name, email address and phone number as well as financial information such as credit card number in order to sign you up for a Hound.com account. Information such as your email address and phone number are collected in order to help Hound serve you better and to communicate information about new offers and schemes, as and when these are announced. 

Hound will absolutely never share any information relating to you with any third parties. Any such information which you provide to us will remain completely confidential. 

Hound.com is one of the 

[_Employment Research Institute_](http://www.employmentresearchinstitute.com/) companies, which also include [_Attorney Resume_](http://www.attorneyresume.com/), [_BCG Attorney Search_](http://www.bcgsearch.com/), [_EdFed_](http://www.edfed.com/), [_Employment Authority_](http://www.employmentauthority.com/), [_General Counsel Consulting_](http://www.gcconsulting.com/), [_Graduate School Loans_](http://www.graduateschoolloans.com/), [_JD2B_](http://www.jd2b.com/), [_Judged_](http://www.judged.com/), [_LawCrossing_](http://www.lawcrossing.com/), [_Law Firm Staff_](http://www.lawfirmstaff.com/), [_Law School Loan Report_](http://www.lawschoolloanreport.org/), [_Law School Loans_](http://www.lawschoolloans.com/), [_Legal Authority_](http://www.legalauthority.com/), [_Legal Authority Financial_](http://www.legalauthorityfinancial.com/), [_Medical School Loans_](http://www.medicalschoolloans.com/), [_Preferred Resumes_](http://www.preferredresumes.com/), and [_Southlake Properties LLC_](http://www.southlakepropertiesllc.com/). Each company is a distinct and separately incorporated entity. The fact that you contacted Hound.com will never be shared with any other Employment Research Institute company or its employees. 

After contacting Hound.com, you may be notified of the potentially complementary services of another Employment Research Institute company. However, the fact that the offer is coming from another Employment Research Institute company will be fully disclosed in the mailing, and you may opt out of such offers at any time as described below. No information will be used for the purposes of such offers except your name, contact address and year of graduation, if applicable, and access to such information will be restricted to the sole purpose of communicating with you. Moreover, all other personal information will absolutely never be shared with any other Employment Research Institute company. 

Opt-out: At any time, you may opt out of receiving emails from Hound.com on our unsubscribe page. Furthermore, you may opt out of receiving emails from other Employment Research Institute companies at any time by clicking on the appropriate "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any such email. 

Like other websites, we use cookies to enhance your visits to our website. Cookies will not be used to collect any personal information or to identify individual visitors. Rather, they may be used to collect information about your browser session, such as time and date, length of session or pages visited. We do not collect any personal information, via our website unless you actually provide such information. 

We use a third-party tracking service (LinkShare) that uses cookies (log files) to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate (usage, volume statistics and referrals) to monitor the traffic flow and provide targeted service referrals. 

While we reserve the right to change our privacy policy, the current policy will always be available on Hound.com. If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding this statement, please email 

[_privacy@hound.com_](mailto:privacy@hound.com). 

**Tell a Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, you are asked to provide a friend's name and email address. Hound.com will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Site. Hound.com does not share this information with any third parties for their promotional purposes. Hound.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program 

**Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews**  
We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. 

**How is the information used?**  
When you supply personal information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose (such as to provide the service or information you have requested). Your contact information may also be used to contact you when necessary in order to respond to your inquiries regarding the service. Every communication with Hound.com is held in strictest confidence and handled with integrity. None of your personal information will be disclosed to a potential employer without you taking affirmative action to disclose this information such as selecting to "apply" for a position within our database. 

Your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties under any circumstances, except as disclosed in this privacy statement. Any general demographic information that we receive will never be utilized to identify you. While it may be used in an aggregated form for research purposes in order to further develop our understanding of the job market or to improve the Web site, none of this demographic information is attributable to your account. This general information may be disseminated or published in its basic form. 

Hound.com will absolutely never share any information relating to your employment situation or resume with any third parties for their promotional purposes. Each employee of Hound.com signs a strict confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement to ensure your privacy. 

Hound.com is one of the Employment Research Institute companies, which include Attorney Research Group, BCG Attorney Search, CLE Authority, EdFed, EmploymentCrossing, General Counsel Consulting, JD Journal, JD2B, Judged, Law Firm Staff, Employment Authority, Preferred Resumes and Southlake Properties LLC. Each company is a distinct and separately incorporated entity, and each company's databases and servers are maintained independently. The fact that you contacted Hound.com will not be shared with any other Employment Research Institute company or its employees unless you opt-into receiving information from any of these affiliated companies such as when you select to use "Resume Service" on our site which takes you to the Preferred Resumes site. Each employee of each company signs a strict confidentiality and nondisclosure agreement, ensuring that they do not disclose your private information to any other person or company. 

After contacting Hound.com, you may be notified of the potentially complementary services of another Employment Research Institute company. However, no information regarding your employment status, or information from your resume, will ever be shared with any other Employment Research Institute company without your explicit consent. Furthermore, the fact that the offer is coming from another Employment Research Institute company will be fully disclosed in the mailing, and you may opt out of such offers at any time as described below. No information will be used for purposes of such offers except your name, email and mailing address and access to such information will be restricted to the sole purpose of communicating with you. 

Should any material changes be made to the manner in which we use personally identifiable information, Hound.com will post the changes on our Web site no less than 30 days prior to a change. This is done in order to give users time to request removal of their information from our database or to make inquiries about any new practices. 

**Security**  
Personally identifiable information is stored on our database and is not publicly accessible. All Hound.com employees must sign non-disclosure contracts that ensure the confidentiality of all personally identifiable information before gaining access to such information. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, and meets or exceeds all industry standards for the protection and confidentiality of personally identifiable information. 

The Hound.com servers use Secure Socket Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that works with Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator (versions 2.0 and higher), Mozilla, Microsoft Internet Explorer (versions 3.0 and higher), and AOL (AOL 3.0 and higher). This encryption provides the best possible protection from unauthorized parties accessing any information you send to us. 

**Correct/Update**  
If you would like to verify the data we have received from you or would like to edit any information you have submitted to us, or if you seek to deactivate the use of your personal information, you may contact us directly at the addresses provided above. You also have the option to make any changes to your resume, job settings, and password in the "My Details" section of the Hound.com main page once you have logged into your account. 

To change your credit card information, please call one of our Customer Service representatives at **626-243-1810**. If your credit card has been lost or has not been granted approval by Verisign, when you attempt to log-in, you will be prompted to sign-up for an account. Simply enter the prior account information along with your new credit card information. All inquiries will receive responses within 30 days of our receipt of them 

If you are concerned about your private information and would like to edit or update it, you may contact us at 

[_contactus@hound.com_](mailto:contactus@hound.com). 

**Links to external pages**  
This site may contain links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website. Hound.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. 

**Service Providers**  
We use a third party, to provide Credit Card Processing for our Site. When you sign up for Hound.com membership, we share your name, username and billing address to process a charge on your credit card. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose. 

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process such as in complying with a subpoena, judicial proceeding or court order served on Hound.com. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

In the event of the sale, merger or acquisition of some or all assets of Hound.com, your personal information would likely be a part of the transferred assets. We shall notify by email or notice on our Site of your choices in how your information is to be used henceforth. 

**Hound.com  
202 S Lake Ave, Unit 250  
Pasadena, CA 91101.**
